http://www.trailspace.com/about/privacy.html

Lumbar Packs
more »
Sleeping Pads
more »
Navigation
Maps
Compasses
GPS
more »
Bivy Sacks
more »
Solid Fuel Stoves
more »
Gear Care and Maintenance
View All Hiking and Camping Gear »
Accessories
View All Climbing Gear »
Paddling Accessories
View All Paddling Gear »
Drinks
View All Running Gear »
Running Snowshoes
more »
Splitboard
more »
Sleds and Pulks
View All Backcountry Snowsports Gear »
Snowsport Socks
more »
Booties
Insoles
Gaiters and Overboots
Traction Devices
View All Footwear »
Snowsport Jackets
more »
Performance Pants and Tights
more »
Vests
Fleece Vests
Down Vests
Synthetic Insulated Vests
more »
Shirts
Hiking Shirts
Running Shirts
more »
Shorts and Skirts
Active Shorts
Hiking Shorts
Hiking Skirts
more »
Base Layers & Underwear
Base Layer Tops
Base Layer Bottoms
more »
Gaiters
View All Outerwear, Clothing, and Accessories »
Brands
Privacy Policy
Individuals who visit the Trailspace website are important to us. Because visitors to our website are important, we do not capture personal information about them without their permission. We endeavor to collect only the minimum amount of information needed to meet the purposes for which the website was created.
Log Files
Like most websites we maintain log files.
The information collected in our log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp.
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web services and help us understand how people are using our services. We analyze our website logs to continually improve the value of the materials available on our site. The information in our website logs is not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link it with the individuals that browse our website.
Personally Identifiable Information
"Personally identifiable information" is information about a person that is readily identifiable to that specific individual. It includes, for example, an individual's name, street address, email address, or phone number.
Personally identifiable information will not be collected unless you voluntarily provide it. For example, by sending an email message, including such information in an online form (such as a gear review, forum message, or member profile), or signing in using a social media account. Your choice not to participate in these activities will not impair your ability to access the information on this website.
Message Boards, Public Forums, and Gear Reviews
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or by signing in with a social media account - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
Cookies
Trailspace may use cookies on a limited basis in order to track your visit to our website or for other purposes. Trailspace does not use cookies to store personally identifiable information.
Some of our business partners (for example, advertisers) may also use cookies on our site. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Trailspace only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Third Party Advertising
The graphical and text-based ads appearing on this website are delivered to users by several Web advertising partners. Information about users' visits to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about our advertising partners and their privacy policies, please follow the links below:
AvantLink Privacy Policy
Commission Junction Privacy Policy
Google Privacy Policy
LinkShare Privacy Policy
Trailspace may use certain features of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, including for Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and/or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by updating your Google Ads Settings.
Trailspace may use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. Trailspace and third-party vendors, including Google, may use first-party and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to the Trailspace website, and/or to report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to the Trailspace website.
Trailspace may use data from Google's interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics.
Trailspace is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.
Disclaimer
Trailspace does not warrant the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published on this website, nor does it endorse any products or services linked from this system, and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Portions of the information may be incorrect or not current. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.
Various websites may be linked through the Trailspace website. Visitors to those sites are advised to check the privacy statements of those sites and be cautious about providing personally identifiable information without a clear understanding of how the information will be used.
Contact Information
To offer comments about the Trailspace website or about information presented in this Privacy Policy, contact us.
